<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News on [HelSec Ry]</title><link>https://helsec.fi/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on [HelSec Ry]</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 23:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://helsec.fi/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Membership applications open</title><link>https://helsec.fi/news/2021-01-04-membership-applications-open/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 23:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://helsec.fi/news/2021-01-04-membership-applications-open/</guid><description>We are open for membership applications!</description></item><item><title>Invitation to HelSec statutory fall meeting</title><link>https://helsec.fi/news/2020-11-26-statutory-fall-meeting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://helsec.fi/news/2020-11-26-statutory-fall-meeting/</guid><description>As HelSec is a registered association, we have to arrange two statutory meetings per year. The COVID-19 situation ruined our initial plans for the fall meeting and as the overall situtation is still unsafe, we decided to have our fall meeting as an online meeting.
All of our members all more than welcome to join the meeting on 26th of November at 17:00 (UTC) / 19:00 (EET). The meeting will be held on Zoom and the meeting information can be found at the end of this email.</description></item><item><title>Invitation to HelSec regular spring meeting</title><link>https://helsec.fi/news/2020-09-03-spring-meeting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 18:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://helsec.fi/news/2020-09-03-spring-meeting/</guid><description>As HelSec is a registered association, we have to arrange two regular meetings per year. The COVID-19 situation ruined our initial plans for the spring meeting and as the overall situtation is still unsafe, we decided to have our spring meeting as an online meeting.
All of our members all more than welcome to join the meeting on 3rd of September at 15:00 (UTC) / 18:00 (EEST). The meeting will be held on Zoom and the meeting information can be found at the end of this email.</description></item><item><title>Nuuksio CTF</title><link>https://helsec.fi/news/2020-06-05-nuuksio-ctf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 17:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://helsec.fi/news/2020-06-05-nuuksio-ctf/</guid><description>Nuuksio CTF: Limited Exposure
As the Finnish government has lifted some restrictions on movement and public gatherings, HelSec announces the first public IRL event since the lockdown measures. The Nuuksio CTF: Limited Exposure is held in the Nuuksio National Park, with a participant limit of 12. We can hack in the woods and shout at each other, no close contact required.
Date: June 5-June 6. If it rains on June 5, then June 6-June 7.</description></item><item><title>HelSec virtual meetup stream setup, part 1</title><link>https://helsec.fi/news/2020-05-11-stream-setup-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 13:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://helsec.fi/news/2020-05-11-stream-setup-1/</guid><description>Our first meetup was a success &amp;ndash; it seems the audience liked it, and from my point of view, the stream setup was easy to use and we didn&amp;rsquo;t break it even once while the stream is running. Due to a few requests, I&amp;rsquo;m documenting our setup so that others can build on it and host their own virtual events with ease.
We couldn&amp;rsquo;t have got this right the first time if not with the valuable input from Dist, Jaroneko, and whois, who had prior experience in working with streams and setting up advanced features and bots on a Discord server.</description></item><item><title>We have 2 tickets to Disobey 2020 to share!</title><link>https://helsec.fi/news/2020-01-20-disobey-tickets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://helsec.fi/news/2020-01-20-disobey-tickets/</guid><description>Did you miss the ticket sales for Disobey 2020? And you still would like to go?
It might be your lucky month! We have two tickets to share with out members. All you need to do is to be a member of our association (more info in HelSec Ry) and fill the form.
The ”chosen ones” will be revealed on 31st of January.</description></item><item><title>Swag!</title><link>https://helsec.fi/news/2019-12-21-swag/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 13:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://helsec.fi/news/2019-12-21-swag/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re finally getting super cool HelSec-swag! Get yours by filling the ~form~ Edit: swag order form closed.</description></item><item><title>Future Female x HelSec: Cyber Security essentials</title><link>https://helsec.fi/news/2019-12-16-futurefemale_x_helsec/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://helsec.fi/news/2019-12-16-futurefemale_x_helsec/</guid><description>HelSec is teaming up with Future Female and Nixu to organize a 6-month training program for women who are interested in working in cyber security or maybe for those already working or studying in this industry but still want to gain deeper knowledge.
Currently there is a global shortage of professionals in the cyber security industry – both male and female. The aim for this program is to enable and empower the women in this field and to attract and find future talent.</description></item></channel></rss>