<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Abouts on [HelSec Ry]</title><link>https://helsec.fi/about/</link><description>Recent content in Abouts on [HelSec Ry]</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><atom:link href="https://helsec.fi/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code of Ethics</title><link>https://helsec.fi/about/coe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://helsec.fi/about/coe/</guid><description>Take control of your choices without fear. Create, shape or modify to improve what’s here. Find your own path and encourage others to find theirs.
Respect privacy Serve and protect the community Share knowledge with the community Act with integrity Avoid conflicts of interest Avoid FUD (Fear Uncertainty and Doubt) Protect everyones data (encryption etc.) Don&amp;rsquo;t be an asshole If you see someone being an asshole contact: security@helsec.fi</description></item><item><title>History</title><link>https://helsec.fi/about/history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://helsec.fi/about/history/</guid><description>Written by whois
Mother of CitySecs - Turku Back in 2018, TurkuSec was super active and lot of people drove there from Helsinki. I had personally been thinking that Helsinki should have similar meetup and started to discuss with Osku about it in TurkuSec August meetup (I think). Turned out, he had thought the same and we agreed that we will start new meetup group in Helsinki. As usually, this was probably beer talking and we did not do anything straight after the meetup.</description></item><item><title>Rules</title><link>https://helsec.fi/about/rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://helsec.fi/about/rules/</guid><description>Currently only in finnish.
1§ Yhdistyksen nimi ja kotipaikka Yhdistyksen nimi on HelSec ry ja sen kotipaikka on Helsinki.
2§ Tarkoitus ja toiminnan laatu Yhdistyksen tarkoituksena on jakaa tietoa ja edistää tieto- ja kyberturvallisuutta ja hyvien tietoturvallisten toimintatapojen noudattamista turvallisuuden kaikilla eri osa-alueilla, toimia jäsentensä yhdyssiteenä ja edistää jäsenten verkostoitumista, sekä tukea jäseniä kehittämään ja ylläpitämään kyberturvallisuuden ammattitaitoa ja laatua.
Tarkoituksensa toteuttamiseksi yhdistys järjestää kokouksia, koulutus- ja keskustelu- ja verkostoitumistilaisuuksia ja vierailuja, harjoittaa tiedotus- ja julkaisutoimintaa, antaa lausuntoja, myöntää tunnustuksia, seuraa kyberturvallisuuden kotimaista ja kansainvälistä kehitystä, sekä pitää yhteyttä muihin järjestöihin, kyberturvallisuuskoulutusta antaviin oppilaitoksiin ja muihin kyberturvallisuuden vaikuttajatahoihin Suomessa ja ulkomailla toimien näiden kanssa yhteistyössä kyberturvallisuuden edistämiseksi.</description></item></channel></rss>